Christopher Beesley

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a solutions focused, team oriented full stack developer with a broad-base of experience and hands-on skills. Successful in troubleshooting software, hardware, and firmware issues. Proven loyalty to company and ability to successfully analyze customers' critical needs, identify deficiencies, and efficiently troubleshoot to remedy problems. Broad understanding of technical hardware and software, and a strong aptitude for new learning.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Field Service Engineer

Tokyo Electron America Oct 2014 - Sep 2017

- Promoted from entry level to lead
- Organized and assigned jobs to co-workers
- Performed troubleshooting and maintenance on hardware, software, and firmware
- Earned several awards for troubleshooting excellence

Technical Sales Rep

Madison Chemical Co Oct 2007 - May 2014

- Promoted from administrative assistant
- Performed audits and suggested process improvements
- In charge of all control systems
- Self-taught PLC programming and similar software
- Integral member of internal audit team for quality management system

SKILLS

HTTML

CSS (Bootstrap)

JavaScript

jQuery

Git

Node.js

MySQL

EDUCATION

Jan - July 2018

Full Stack Coding Program

University of Kansas

Expected Finish July 2018

2003 - 2007

Bachelor of Arts, Major in Theology

Hanover College